tribuna.com 2019-12-08

# Tribuna.com

### Application privacy statement

This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) applies to the treatment of personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from, you in connection with the associated application (“Application”). The Application is provided by Tribuna Digital (and may be provided by Tribuna Digital on behalf of a Tribuna Digital licensor or partner (“Application Partner”). By using or otherwise accessing the Application, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

### What personal information does Tribuna Digital collect?

We collect the following types of information from our users:

#### Personal Information You Provide to Us:

We may receive and store any information you submit to the Application (or otherwise authorize us to obtain – such as, from (for example) your Facebook account). The types of personal information collected may include:

  * your full name
  * email address
  * link on your pic from Facebook/Google (if you logged in)
  * Facebook ID or Google (if you logged in)
  * IP address
  * browser information
  * username
  * comments and content you made
  * data about the manufacturer, model, operating system version of your mobile device, screen resolution
  * advertising identifies
  * language you chose in your app
  * events and visits

#### How does Tribuna Digital use the information it collects?

Tribuna Digital uses the information described in this Privacy Statement internally, to analyze, develop and improve its products and services, and (ii) as set forth below in the “Will Tribuna Digital Share any of the personal information it Collects” section below.

### Application partner treatment of personal information

Tribuna Digital may provide personal information to the applicable Application Partner. The Application Partner’s use of your personal information is subject to the Application Partner’s separate privacy policy – and not this Privacy Statement.

We contractually require all Application Partners to treat your personal information as confidential information and to only use it for the services we need. However, we do not have direct control over how Application Partners use your personal information and we cannot guarantee that our Application Partners will use your personal information as required in our contract with them. For this reason, we are not responsible for our Application Partners misuse of your personal information.

### How is my personal information used for analytics?

As an online business, it is important for us to know how users interact with our website and apps. We and our Application Partners will collect your Location Information, Device Information, and Advertising IDs so that we can deliver our services to our users, measure, analyze, and improve performance of our products, and to continually update and develop it. Here you can find the full list of analytics partners:

### For web:

  * Google Analytics, privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>
  * Yandex.Metrika, privacy policy: <https://yandex.com/legal/privacy/>

### For mobile apps:

  * AppMetrika, privacy policy: <https://yandex.com/legal/privacy/>
  * Google Analytics, privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>
  * Firebase, privacy policy: <https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy>
  * Facebook Analytics, privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

### How is my personal information used for advertising?

To help us keep our site and apps running, we show ads with the help of third-party advertising partners (“Ad Partners”). We integrate their technologies into our products which are then used by the Ad Partners to determine what kind of ads to display to you.

### Do Ad Partners Collect My Personal Information?

In order to show you ads that you might interesting and/or relevant ("Targeted Ads"), Ad Partners collect and use your Advertising ID, Location Information, and Device Information. If location services are enabled in your Device settings, the Ad Partners may additionally collect your geolocation information. Because these Ad Partners' technologies control what kind of personal information is collected from your Device and how it is used, we encourage you to review their respective privacy policies.

#### Our Ad Partners:

  * Google Ad Manager, privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>
  * Mopub, privacy policy: <https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/>
  * Facebook, privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>
  * InMobi, privacy policy: <https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy-for-eea>

### How to Opt-Out of Receiving Targeted Ads?

For more information you can checkout our Cookie Policy: <https://tribuna.com/en/cookie_policy>

### Will Tribuna Digital share any of the personal information it receives?

Personal information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone (with the exception of sharing your information with an applicable Application Partner – see the “Application Partner Treatment” section above). We share your personal information only as described below.

Application Partners: We will share your personal information with an applicable Application Partner (see the “Application Partner Treatment” section above).

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Tribuna Digital’s agents do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of personal information for the above purposes.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Tribuna Digital, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Tribuna Digital goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Tribuna Digital may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of Tribuna Digital and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Tribuna Digital, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

### How long will Tribuna Digital keep my personal information?

How long we store your personal information will depend on the purpose that we originally collected it. We will not retain personal information for longer than is necessary for our business or for legal requirements, but in any case no more than 60 months from the moment of the last user activity in the Application.

### Push notifications

After downloading our App, you will be asked to accept or refuse push notifications. If you accept push notifications, we will collect and use push notification tokens to send you notifications on your mobile device. You may disable push notifications at any time by going to your App settings.

### Conditions of use

If you decide to use or otherwise access the Application, your use/access and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

### How do I access or manage my personal data?

If you want to update or manage the personal data that Tribuna Digital has collected about you, please, contact us at [support.90live@tribuna.com](mailto:%20support.90live@tribuna.com)

### Who can use the application?

Our site, Application and the services available through Tribuna Digital are not intended for persons under the age of 13. Tribuna Digital does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents’ consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child’s web experience.

### Changes to this privacy statement

Tribuna Digital may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when he or she uses or otherwise accesses the Application after such changes have been first posted.

### Questions or concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at [support.90live@tribuna.com](mailto:%20support.90live@tribuna.com) We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
